<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<!-- Stews -->
	
	
	<AC_InsertProduceDesc>Produce to Insert</AC_InsertProduceDesc>
	<AC_StartInsertion>Bring Produce</AC_StartInsertion>
	<AC_StartInsertionDesc>Bring produce to the artisan fermenter to start processing</AC_StartInsertionDesc>
	<AC_CancelBringingProduce>Cancel Bringing Produce</AC_CancelBringingProduce>
	<AC_CancelBringingProduceDesc>Cancel bringing produce to the artisan fermenter.</AC_CancelBringingProduceDesc>
	<AC_VinegarFailurePower>The product has spoiled due to a power failure in the artisan fermenter</AC_VinegarFailurePower>
	<AC_CaskNotWorking>This artisan fermenter is not working at the moment</AC_CaskNotWorking>
	<AC_InfuserNotWorking>This infuser is not working at the moment</AC_InfuserNotWorking>
	<AC_CantRunQuest>Quest can't be run at the moment (likely culprit: no allies in the world to offer it)</AC_CantRunQuest>

	<AC_DisableQuests>Disable Artisan Trading quests</AC_DisableQuests>
	<AC_DisableQuests_Description>Disables Artisan Trading quests from triggering. Bear in mind these quests are independent of any other quests or storyteller events (raids, manhunters, etc). They don't "take a slot"</AC_DisableQuests_Description>
	<AC_QuestRate>Artisan Trading quest multiplier (lower means getting the event more often)</AC_QuestRate>
	<AC_QuestRateTooltip>The frequency of the Artisan Trading quest being offered is multiplied by this number (with a multiplier of 1, it is offered every between 15 and 30 days at random). Numbers below 1 decrease the time, while numbers above it increase it. Note that this event doesn't "replace" normal quests, it works independently.</AC_QuestRateTooltip>
	<AC_MarketValueModifier>Artisan goods market value modifier</AC_MarketValueModifier>
	<AC_MarketValueModifierTooltip>The market value of artisan goods will be multiplied by this rate. 0.1 means artisan goods will be basically worthless, while 5 will quintuple their value, and therefore the profit. Make millionaires out of fermented fish, I don't care!</AC_MarketValueModifierTooltip>
	<AC_StatsReport_ArtisanProduct>Artisan product mod options modifier x{0}</AC_StatsReport_ArtisanProduct>
	<AC_Reset>Reset</AC_Reset>
	<AC_UseDropdownForMachines>Use dropdown designator for machines (requires game reload)</AC_UseDropdownForMachines>
	<AC_UseDropdownForMachines_Description>If this is ON, all buildings added by this mod will appear under a single designator for the artisan workshop, and clicking on it will bring up a dropdown menu to select the rest. OFF by default as it confused people. Requires game reload.</AC_UseDropdownForMachines_Description>
	
	<AC_CondimentEffects>Condiment Effects</AC_CondimentEffects>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsTitle>Acting as condiment (if VE Cooking is present)</AC_CondimentEffectsTitle>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsButter>A rich, creamy dairy product made by churning cream, commonly used in cooking, baking, and as a spread. It gives a 10% bonus to Blood pumping for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsButter>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsSourCream>A tangy, creamy dairy product made by curdling milk with vinegar, offering a rich texture and flavor perfect for enhancing both savory and sweet dishes. Provides +5% Immunity Gain Speed for 12 hours for a probiotic benefit but slightly decreases Move Speed due to its richness.</AC_CondimentEffectsSourCream>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsButtermilk>A tangy, slightly thickened dairy product made by combining milk with lemon juice, commonly used in baking and cooking to add moisture and a subtle acidity to recipes. Provides +12% Injury Healing Factor; however, slightly reduces Social Impact for its acquired taste.</AC_CondimentEffectsButtermilk>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsCondensedMilk>A thick, sweetened dairy product made by reducing milk, commonly used in desserts, baking, or as a long-lasting ingredient for various recipes. Provides +15% Psychic Sensitivity for a mood-lifting sweetness, but also +5% Rest Fall Rate as it makes the consumer feel sluggish.</AC_CondimentEffectsCondensedMilk>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsVinegar>A sharp, acidic liquid created by fermenting produce, used for cooking, preserving food, and crafting artisan goods. Boosts toxin resistance by 10% for 12 hours, aligning with its cleansing qualities.</AC_CondimentEffectsVinegar>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsFishSauce>A savory, fermented liquid made from fish, commonly used as a flavorful condiment. +8% Manipulation for 12 hours, enhances dexterity for cooking and crafting, but lowers Social impact due to its strong smell.</AC_CondimentEffectsFishSauce>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsMiso>A traditional paste made by fermenting soybeans with koji, known for its rich, savory flavor. Provides +5% Psychic Sensitivity and +5% Blood Filtration for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsMiso>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsBlackGarlic>Black garlic is a type of aged garlic that undergoes a fermentation-like process, resulting in soft, dark-colored cloves. Provides very mild regeneration of wounds for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsBlackGarlic>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsFlour>A finely ground powder made from non-wheat sources such as nuts, seeds, or alternative grains. Increases mood by 3 for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsFlour>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsZest>The outer peel of citrus fruits, rich in aromatic oils and vibrant flavors. Provides a bright flavor boosting joy, lowering Joy fall rate factor for 10% for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsZest>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsCornSyrup>A sweetener made from corn starch, processed to convert some of its glucose into fructose. Provides a large +20% Moving bonus, but also lowers Manipulation by 5% for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsCornSyrup>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsMolasses>A thick, dark syrup created as a byproduct of the sugar refining process, especially from sugarcane. Provides a 5% bonus to Global learning factor and a 5% Rest fall rate factor reduction for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsMolasses>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsEssence>A concentrated extract derived from the purest flavors or aromas of ingredients like fruits, herbs, or spices. Makes you refreshed and ready to harvest some kidneys or something, giving a 5% bonus to Medical tend speed and Medical operation speed for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsEssence>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsJam>A sweet spread made by cooking fruits with sugar, jam preserves the flavors of ripe fruit while creating a thick, spreadable consistency. Makes you forget your problems for a while, reducing the duration of negative memories by 20% for 2 days.</AC_CondimentEffectsJam>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsGhee>A clarified butter with a rich, nutty flavor, prized for its high smoke point and long shelf life. It gives a 12% bonus to Blood pumping and a 2.5% bonus to immunity gain speed for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsGhee>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsGravy>A rich, savory sauce made by combining meat drippings with flavorful stock, thickened for a smooth texture and bold flavor. Increases animal gather speed and yield for 10% for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsGravy>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsOil>A versatile, high-quality liquid used for cooking, crafting, and various artisan processes. Increases toxic environment resistance for 10% for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsOil>
	<AC_CondimentEffectsInfusedOil>Infused oil is crafted by steeping rich oil with herbal medicine or aromatic spices inside an infuser. Increases toxic environment resistance for 20% for 12 hours.</AC_CondimentEffectsInfusedOil>

</LanguageData>